Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts, 1928-1958 RL.00655
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Eastman Kodak, 1930-1954; 14
  - Kodak Family Adventure, approximately 1954; 15
    - The Osborne Crisis, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Osbornes Go House-Hunting, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Osbornes Look for a Home, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The San Francisco Story, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Summons Home, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Teche County and Avery Island, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Trip to Cooperstown, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
  - Other Programming, 1930-1947; 16
    - Angelo Patri, recorded programs, 1934 May-Aug. (Film-reel 132)
      WTAM, WWJ
    - Commercials, 1945 Jan.-1946 Apr. (Film-reel 275)
    - Commercials, 1947 Jan.-Sept. (Film-reel 419)
    - Dr. Haggard--Devils--Drugs--Doctors, 1931 Jan.-1932 Jan. (Film-reel 132)
    - Kodak Mid-Week Hour, 1930 Apr.-July (Film-reel 131)
    - Kodak Weekend Hour, 1930 Apr.-June (Film-reel 131)
    - Kodak Weekend Hour, 1931 Apr.-Sept. (Film-reel 131)
    - Kodak Weekend Hour, 1932 Apr.-Sept. (Film-reel 131)
    - Kodak Weekend Hour, coastal stations, 1931 Mar.-July (Film-reel 131)
    - Kodak Weekend Hour, coastal stations, 1932 May-Sept. (Film-reel 131)
    - Musical Pictures, 1942 Nov. (Film-reel 174)
    - Spot announcements, 1946 Feb.-Dec. (Film-reel 305)
- Elgin National Watch Co., 1936-1948; 15
  - Adventures of Nero Wolfe, 1944 Jan.-May 12 (Film-reel 234)
    Jan. 21 (#1) and June 30 (#24) never received from Chicago; Nero Wolfe also on J.B. Williams Co. program Apr.7-Sept. 27, 1943 (reel 207)
  - Adventures of Nero Wolfe, 1944 May 19-July 14 (Film-reel 235)
  - Christmas Show, 1948 Dec. 25 (Film-reel 419)
  - Football Revue, 1936 May-Dec. (Film-reel 154)
  - Recording of 75th Anniversary Celebration at World's Fair, 1939 Aug. 18 (Film-reel 154)
  - Thanksgiving Show, 1948 Nov.25 (Film-reel 419)
- Emerson Drug Co. (Bromo-Seltzer), 1935-1948; 16
  - Commercials, 1935-1948; 17
    - Canada, Let's Disagree, 1939 Oct.-1940 Mar. (Film-reel 421)
    - Robert Shaw Chorale, 1948 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 421)
    - Tito Guiza, 1936 Feb.-Mar. (Film-reel 421)
    - Tom Howard, 1936 Jan. (Film-reel 421)
    - 1939 Nov.-1940 Feb. (Film-reel 171)
    - 1938 Apr.-June (Film-reel 244)
      Many missing
    - 1935 Apr.-May (Film-reel 421)
    - 1938 Jan.-June (Film-reel 421)
  - Other Programming, 1935-1940; 18
    - Canada, E. Maloney writer, undated (Film-reel 421)
    - Grenlund and His Girls, 1935 Aug. 20 (Film-reel 342)
    - Harriet Parsons, 1938 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 342)
    - Spot announcements, 1936 Feb.-1938 Apr. (Film-reel 244)
    - 1935-1940 (Film-reel 13)
    - 1935 July-1936 Jan. (Film-reel 244)
- Fanny Farmer Candies, 1942-1951; 17
  - Buffalo Billy, 1950-1951; 19
    - 1950 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 736)
    - 1951 Jan. 714 (Film-reel 788)
    - 1950 Oct.-1951 Jan. (Film-reel 1007)
  - Commercials, 1942-1948; 20
    - Spot announcements, 1942 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 201)
    - Station breaks, 1943 Nov.-1945 (Film-reel 261)
    - Station breaks, 1945 (Film-reel 262)
    - 1942 July-Sept. (Film-reel 170)
    - 1942 Aug.-1943 Oct. (Film-reel 209)
    - 1946 (Film-reel 305)
    - 1947 (Film-reel 366)
    - 1947 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 418)
    - 1948 Jan.-Sept. (Film-reel 419)
- Ford Dealers of America, 1948-1950; 18
  - College of Musical Knowledge, 1949 Dec.-1950 Nov. (Film-reel 735)
    Part of Nov. 30
  - College of Musical Knowledge, 1950 Nov.-30-Dec. (Film-reel 736)
    Rest of Nov. 30
  - Dickens' Christmas Carol, 1949 Dec. 24-25 (Film-reel 717)
  - Dr. Marshall, 1950 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 736)
  - Fred Allen Show, 1948 Jan.-June; Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 419)
  - Fred Allen Show, 1949 Jan.-June (Film-reel 734)
  - Saturday News, 1950 Dec. (Film-reel 736)
  - Spot announcements, 1949 Jan. (Film-reel 717)
  - Spot announcements, 1949 (Film-reel 734)
  - Through the Crystal Ball, 1949 Apr.-June (Film-reel 734)
  - Variety Show, 1949 June-July (Film-reel 734)
- Ford Motor Company, 1944-1955; 19
  - Ford Festival, 1951-1952; 21
    - James Melton, 1951 Apr. 5-1952 June 26 (Film-reel 974)
    - James Melton, 1951 Apr. 5-1952 June 26 (Film-reel 976)
      Beginning of reel fogged; done over on reel 977
    - James Melton, 1951 Apr. 5 (Film-reel 976)
    - James Melton, 1952 June 26 (Film-reel 977)
    - Mr. Peepers, 1952 July 3-Sept. 11 (Film-reel 974)
    - Mr. Peepers, 1952 July 3-Sept. 11 (Film-reel 976)
  - Other Programming, 1944-1955; 22
    - Bill Ingram News--Cars, trucks, 1953 (Film-reel 982)
    - Bob Crosby Show, 1946 Jan.-July (Film-reel 305)
    - Calypso, 1947 July-Aug. (Film-reel 419)
    - Commercials, 1944 Apr. (Film-reel 215)
    - Commercials, 1947 (Film-reel 362)
    - Commercials, 1948 Mar.-May (Film-reel 419)
    - Dodger baseball, commercials, 1948 (Film-reel 419)
    - Economy truck radio commercials, 1953 (Film-reel 982)
    - Ford dealer spots, 1946 Oct. 29-31 (Film-reel 307)
    - Ford dealer spots--Car, radio, 1953 (Film-reel 982)
    - Ford promotion spots, 1945 Sept. 15 (Film-reel 275)
    - Ford Star Jubilee television, 1956 (Film-reel 1003)
    - Ford Star Jubilee--Television, 1955 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 1001)
    - Ford Star Jubilee--The Caine Mutiny Court Marshal, 1955 Nov. 19 (Film-reel 1001)
    - Ford Star Theater scripts, 1951 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 788)
    - Ford TV individual dealer purchase, 1949-1950 (Film-reel 982)
    - Frances Greer, 1945 Apr.-June (Film-reel 275)
    - Import sales, 1948 Oct. 11 (Film-reel 419)
    - Lincoln-Mercury, 1947 Dec. (Film-reel 419)
    - Music Report for Motion Pictures, 1953 July 8 (Film-reel 982)
    - Recorded spot, 1948 Mar. 8 (Film-reel 427)
    - Robert Trout News--Car, commercials, 1952-1953 (Film-reel 982)
    - Shooting scripts--Cars, trucks, 1953 (Film-reel 982)
    - Spot announcements--Houston simulcast Eastern Parkway Boxing, 1953 (Film-reel 982)
    - Spot announcements--Time Savers, 1953 July 7 (Film-reel 982)
    - Stars of the Future, 1944 Dec. (Film-reel 235)
    - Stars of the Future, 1945 (Film-reel 275)
    - Television auditions, 1948 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 419)
    - Trucks, 1947 Dec. (Film-reel 419)
    - Used Car and Truck Service, 1953 (Film-reel 982)
  - The Ford Show, 1946-1947; 23
    - Dinah Shore, 1947 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 361)
    - Dinah Shore, 1947 Apr.-June (Film-reel 362)
    - 1946 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 305)
    - 1946 Dec. (Film-reel 307)
- General Cigars, 1931-1950; 20
  - Robert Burns Panatela, 1932-1933; 24
    - Burns & Allen, 1932 Feb.-1933 May (Film-reel 149)
  - White Owl Cigars, 1931-1950; 25
    - Broadcast, 1934 Mar.-1935 Sept. (Film-reel 150)
    - Burns & Allen, 1933 May-1934 Mar. (Film-reel 149)
    - Burns & Allen, 1931-1933 (Film-reel 343)
    - Commercials, 1944 June; Dec. (Film-reel 215)
    - Earl Wilson Show, 1945 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 275)
    - Earl Wilson Show, 1945 Mar.-July (Film-reel 275)
    - Fred H. Ferrar (trumpet), 1939 Apr. 13 (Film-reel 175)
    - Hendrick Van Loon, 1940 Dec. 27-1941 Jan. 10 (Film-reel 176)
    - International Cigar, 1945 Oct. 24 (Film-reel 366)
    - News--Henry Gladstone, 1944 Jan.-1945 Jan. (Film-reel 242)
      No broadcasts Mar. 23-June 12, 15; Sept. 21, Oct. 5 and 12, Nov. 2 and 6
    - Quentin Reynolds and Bennett Cerf audition, 1945 May 7 (Film-reel 361)
    - Raymond Clapper--Commercials, London and Algeria broadcasts, 1943 (Film-reel 208)
    - Raymond Grave Swing, 1939 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 175)
    - Raymond Grave Swing, 1940 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 175)
      No broadcast Jan. 8; missing May 15, June 24-26 broadcasts
    - Raymond Grave Swing, 1940 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 176)
    - Raymond Grave Swing, 1941-1942 (Film-reel 176)
    - Sports Program, 1939 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 153)
    - Spot announcements, 1940 Apr. 15 (Film-reel 175)
    - White Owl Sports Smoker, 1947 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 367)
    - White Owl Sports Smoker, 1948 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 422)
    - World's Fair exhibit building recording, 1940 May 2 (Film-reel 175)
    - Yankee Baseball, 1948 Mar.-Sept. (Film-reel 422)
    - Yankee Baseball commercial, 1947 Apr.-July (Film-reel 366)
    - Yankee Baseball commercial, 1947 July-Sept. (Film-reel 367)
    - Yankees baseball, 1946 Mar.-July (Film-reel 313)
    - Yankees baseball, 1946 July-Sept. (Film-reel 314)
    - Yankees baseball, 1948 Sept.-Oct. (Film-reel 422)
    - Yankees baseball, 1949-1950 (Film-reel 719)
- Groves (Bromo-Quinine), 1940-1941; 21
  - Commercials, 1940-1941; 26
    - Spot announcements, 1940 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 175)
    - 1941 Oct.-Nov. (Film-reel 170)
    - 1940 Sept.-1941 Jan. (Film-reel 174)
    - 1941 Oct.-1942 Jan. (Film-reel 205)
    - 1941 Oct.-1942 Jan. (Film-reel 206)
- J.B. Williams, 1938-1949; 22
  - Aqua Velva, 1939-1941; 27
    - Commercials, 1939 Sept.-Oct. (Film-reel 153)
    - Spot announcements, 1940 July-Aug.; 1941 Jan.-Sept. (Film-reel 182)
  - CBS News, 1946; 28
    - KFH, WINR, WHP, WGBF, commercials, 1946 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 314)
    - William L. Shirer commercials, 1946 (Film-reel 314)
    - WTIC, commercials, 1946 (Film-reel 314)
  - Glider, 1938-1948; 29
    - Bob Howard, 1938 (Film-reel 153)
    - Commercials, 1948 Jan.-June (Film-reel 418)
    - Sports Program, A.B McGinley, WTIC, 1938 Apr.-Sept. (Film-reel 153)
    - Swing Program, 1938 Apr.-1939 Feb. (Film-reel 153)
    - Swing Program, Bob Howard, 1939 Mar.-Oct. (Film-reel 154)
    - Walgreen Drug commercials, 1941 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 182)
      WIND, WENR, WGN
    - William Cunningham Participation program, commercials, 1940 (Film-reel 181)
    - William Cunningham Participation program, commercials, 1940 (Film-reel 182)
      Gift cake of Lanoline soap
    - William L. Shirer, 1943 Dec.-1945 Dec. (Film-reel 264)
      Many dates missing
    - WQXR, 1943 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 264)
    - WQXR, 1944 Jan.-June (Film-reel 265)
    - WTIC, 1943 Sept.-1945 Dec. (Film-reel 264)
  - Glider, Aqua Velva, 1941-1944; 30
    - Commercials, 1942 Jan.-Sept.; 1943 Mar.-Sept. (Film-reel 207)
    - Latin American program, WLWO, commercials, 1941 July-1942 Aug. (Film-reel 243)
      In Spanish
    - Nero Wolf, 1943 Apr.-Sept. (Film-reel 207)
    - William L. Shirer News, commercials, 1944 Jan.-Nov. (Film-reel 242)
      Missing Mar. 19
    - William L. Shirer News, commercials, 1944 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 243)
  - Other Programming, 1940-1949; 31
    - Act II, 1949 Mar.-July (Film-reel 718)
    - Commercials, 1945 (Film-reel 283)
    - Commercials, 1947 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 365)
    - Commercials--Latin American program, 1940 Aug.-1941 July (Film-reel 182)
    - Eddie Mayehoff Looks at the News audition, 1947 Apr. 1 (Film-reel 361)
    - Frank Sinatra--Commercials, 1943 Dec. (Film-reel 207)
    - Say It With Acting, 1949 Aug.-Oct. (Film-reel 718)
    - Say It With Acting, 1949 Oct.-1950 Aug. (Film-reel 719)
      No script for July 30
    - Talks, 1945 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 283)
    - True Or False program--Dr. Harry Hagen, 1943 Jan.-June (Film-reel 207)
    - William L. Shirer, 1943 Dec. (Film-reel 207)
    - William L. Shirer, news, 1945 (Film-reel 283)
  - Pearson & Allen, 1940; 32
    - Washington Merry Go-Round, 1940 July-Sept. (Film-reel 181)
    - Washington Merry Go-Round, 1940 July-Sept. (Film-reel 182)
  - Ted Steele, 1940; 33
    - Gliding Swing program, 1940 Jan.-July (Film-reel 181)
    - Gliding Swing program, 1940 Jan.-July (Film-reel 182)
  - Williams News Program, 1940-1942; 34
    - WQXR, 1940-1942 (Film-reel 181)
    - WQXR, 1940 Feb.-Aug.; 1942 Feb.-Aug. (Film-reel 182)
    - WQXR, 1940 Jan.-July (Film-reel 182)
    - WTIC, 1940-1941 Sept. (Film-reel 181)
    - WTIC, 1940 Jan.-1941 Sept. (Film-reel 182)
      Rota-Shaver, Aqua Velva, Glider
    - WTIC, 1940 May 1-2 (Film-reel 182)
  - Williams Shaving Cream, 1938-1942; 35
    - True Or False program, Dr. Harry Hagen, 1940 Jan.-1942 Nov. (Film-reel 181)
      No broadcasts in summer
    - True Or False program, Dr. Harry Hagen, 1942 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 181)
    - True Or False program, Dr. Harry Hagen, 1942 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 182)
    - True or False, Dr. Harry Hagen, 1938-1939 (Film-reel 153)
    - WFIL commercials, 1941 Sept. 16 (Film-reel 181)
    - WFIL commercials, 1941 Sept. 16 (Film-reel 182)
- Johns-Manville Company, 1933-1954; 23
  - Bill Henry News, 1943-1954; 36
    - 1943 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 206)
    - 1944 (Film-reel 235)
      No broadcast July 11-21
    - 1945 (Film-reel 276)
      Missing Jan. 1, Dec. 20 broadcasts
    - 1946 (Film-reel 306)
    - 1947 (Film-reel 362)
    - 1947 Dec.-1948 Apr. (Film-reel 420)
    - 1948 May-Dec. (Film-reel 421)
      No broadcasts June 21-Aug. 20
    - 1949 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 734)
    - 1954 (Film-reel 992)
  - Cecil Brown News, 1942-1943; 37
    - 1942 June-July (Film-reel 173)
    - 1942 July-Dec. (Film-reel 174)
    - 1943 Jan.-Sept. (Film-reel 206)
    - 1942 Dec. 23 (Film-reel 206)
  - Commercials, 1940-1952; 38
    - WGY, 1940 Apr.-July (Film-reel 173)
    - WMCA, 1940 Aug. (Film-reel 173)
    - 1944 Dec. 28 (Film-reel 215)
    - 1952 (Film-reel 982)
  - Fair Meadows USA, 1951-1952; 39
    - 1951 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 789)
    - 1951 Dec. 16-23 (Film-reel 982)
      Episodes 78
    - 1952 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 982)
  - Other Programming, 1933-1952; 40
    - Advancing Human Frontier television, 1952 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 910)
    - Advancing Human Frontier television, 1952 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 911)
    - Audition, 1941 Dec. 23 (Film-reel 175)
    - Dramatic, 1936 Jan. 13 (Film-reel 155)
    - Floyd Gibbons, 1933 Oct.-1935 June (Film-reel 154)
    - Floyd Gibbons, 1935 June-July (Film-reel 155)
    - Institutional radio talks, 1937 (Film-reel 155)
    - News scripts, 1951 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 788)
    - News scripts, 1951 Mar.-Dec. (Film-reel 789)
    - News--Elma Davis, 1942 Jan.-June (Film-reel 173)
      Feb. 12 missing
    - News--Elma Davis, 1942 Feb. 12 (Film-reel 206)
    - News--Frazier Hunt, 1941 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 173)
- Kellogg Co., 1938-1942; 24
  - Howie Wing--A Saga of Aviation, WABC, 1938-1939; 41
    - 1938 Oct. (Film-reel 156)
      First 10 episodes; agency was N.W. Ayer
    - 1938 Nov.-1939 May (Film-reel 157)
    - 1939 May-June (Film-reel 158)
  - Other Programming, 1939-1942; 42
    - Commercials, 1942 (Film-reel 175)
    - Corn Flakes commercials, Latin America, 1941 July 30 (Film-reel 170)
    - The Circle, 1939 Jan.-July (Film-reel 156)
- Kraft Cheese, 1929-1958; 25
  - Kraft Music Hall, 1933-1955; 43
    - Al Jolson, 1947 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 363)
    - Al Jolson, 1948 Jan.-June (Film-reel 423)
    - Al Jolson, 1948 June; Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 424)
    - Bing Crosby, 1944 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 235)
      Missing Apr. 13, May 11, Oct. 26 broadcasts
    - Bing Crosby, 1944 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 236)
    - Bing Crosby, etc., 1940 Jan.-1941 Jan. (Film-reel 177)
      No broadcast June 27 due to Republican Convention
    - Bing Crosby, etc., 1941 Jan.-1942 Feb. (Film-reel 178)
      Missing Feb. 5 1942 broadcast
    - Bing Crosby, etc., 1942 Jan.-Dec. (Film-reel 179)
    - Bing Crosby, etc., 1943 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 205)
      Missing Nov.-Dec. 23; missing July 1, 1943
    - Bing Crosby, etc., 1941 July-1943 Dec. (Film-reel 214)
    - Commercials, 1934 Sept.-Oct. (Film-reel 121)
    - Eddy Duchin, 1947 Jan.-June (Film-reel 363)
    - Jimmy Dorsey, Bing Crosby, 1935 Dec.-1936 Feb. (Film-reel 121)
    - Jimmy Dorsey, Bing Crosby, 1936 (Film-reel 122)
    - Jimmy Dorsey, Bing Crosby, 1937 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 123)
    - Jimmy Dorsey, Bing Crosby, 1937 Apr.-July (Film-reel 124)
    - John Trotter Orchestra, Bing Crosby, 1938 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 122)
    - John Trotter Orchestra, Bing Crosby, 1938 Mar.-Dec. (Film-reel 123)
    - John Trotter Orchestra, Bing Crosby, 1937 July-Dec.; 1939 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 124)
    - John Trotter Orchestra, Bing Crosby, 1939 Mar.-Dec. (Film-reel 125)
    - John Trotter Orchestra, Bing Crosby, 1939 Mar. 1623 (Film-reel 127)
    - Nelson Eddy, 1947 July-Sept. (Film-reel 363)
    - Paul Whiteman, Al Jolson, Deems Taylor, 1933 June-1934 July (Film-reel 120)
    - Paul Whiteman, Al Jolson, Deems Taylor, 1934 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 121)
    - Paul Whiteman, Al Jolson, Deems Taylor, 1935 (Film-reel 121)
    - Rudy Vallee, radio, 1955 Feb.-Sept. (Film-reel 1001)
    - 1949 Jan.-May (Film-reel 722)
  - Kraft Television Theatre, 1947-1958; 44
    - 1947 May 7-June 25 (Film-reel 363)
      Through second act of June 25 I Like It Here
    - A Bit o' Love, 1955 Jan. 6 (Film-reel 1000)
    - A Christmas Carol, 1952 Dec. 24 (Film-reel 908)
    - A Kiss for Cinderella, 1952 Oct. 15 (Film-reel 908)
    - A Long Night in Forty Mile, 1952 Oct. 22 (Film-reel 908)
    - A Matter of Life, 1957 Apr. 17 (Film-reel 1002)
    - A Night of Rain, 1957 Apr. 24 (Film-reel 1002)
    - A Night To Remember, 1956 Mar. 28 (Film-reel 1004)
    - A Night To Remember, 1956 May 2 (Film-reel 1004)
    - A Nugget from the Sunset, 1955 Dec. 15 (Film-reel 1001)
    - A Profile in Courage, 1956 May 16 (Film-reel 1004)
    - A Seacoast in Bohemia, 1955 Apr. 27 (Film-reel 1000)
    - A Traveler from Brussels, 1957 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 1002)
    - A Woman for Tony, 1955 June 1 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Accusation, 1957 Dec. 30 (Film-reel 1011)
    - All Those Beautiful Girls, 1957 May 29 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Amy, 1958 Feb. 12 (Film-reel 1011)
    - Angry Angel, 1958 Mar. 26 (Film-reel 1008)
    - Anna Santonello, 1956 Aug. 8 (Film-reel 1004)
    - At Mrs. Beam's, 1952 June 4 (Film-reel 907)
    - Babies For Sale, 1956 July 18 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Background, 1952 Sept. 24 (Film-reel 907)
    - Bed Room 12 on the Appalachian Waterfall, 1956 May 23 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Before It's Too Late, 1956 Nov. 14 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Bobbie, 1956 Feb. 29 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Box Seven-O-Four, 1956 May 30 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Boy In a Cage, 1956 June 13 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Boy Will Be Boys, 1955 Jan. 26 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Christmas Dinner, 1955 Dec. 21 (Film-reel 1001)
    - Code of the Corner, 1958 Jan. 15 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Collision, 1957 Mar. 13 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Country Music, undated (Film-reel 1011)
    - Cricket on the Hearth, 1952 June 11 (Film-reel 907)
    - Day of Judgment, 1955 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 1001)
    - Death is a Spanish Dancer, 1956 May 9 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Death of Kid Slawson, 1952 June 18 (Film-reel 907)
    - Departure, 1955 Feb. 16 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Divorcees Anonymous, undated (Film-reel 1011)
    - Dog in a Bush Tunnel, 1958 Mar. 5 (Film-reel 1008)
    - Drop on the Devil, 1955 June 22 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Drummer Man, 1957 May 1 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Eddie (missing), 1958 Jan. 22 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Eleven O'Clock Flight, 1955 Dec. 23 (Film-reel 1001)
    - Fire and Ice, 1957 June 12 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Five Minutes To Live, 1956 Feb. 2 (Film-reel 1003)
    - Flesh and Blood, 1957 May 8 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Flowers for 2B, 1955 May 4 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Flying Object at 3 O'Clock High, 1956 June 20 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Follow the Dream, 1952 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 906)
    - Give Me the Courage, 1957 Feb. 20 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Good Old Charlie Faye, 1956 Feb. 8 (Film-reel 1003)
    - Gramercy Ghost, 1955 Apr. 20 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Green Cars Go East, 1952 Apr. 16 (Film-reel 906)
    - Half the World's a Bride, 1955 Mar. 2 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Hang Up My Guns, 1957 Jan. 2 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Haunted, 1955 Aug. 24 (Film-reel 1003)
    - Hilda McKay, 1952 Nov. 12 (Film-reel 908)
    - Hit and Run, 1956 Oct. 31 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Home Is the Hero, 1956 Jan. 25 (Film-reel 1003)
    - I Am 15--And I Don't Want to Die, 1956 Oct. 17 (Film-reel 1004)
    - I Woke Up Stupid, 1958 Jan. 15 (Film-reel 1011)
    - I, Mrs. Bibb, 1955 Oct. 19 (Film-reel 1003)
    - Impasse, 1955 July 6 (Film-reel 1002)
    - In Albert's Room, 1953 Aug. 19 (Film-reel 1003)
    - In the LaBanza, 1955 July 20 (Film-reel 1003)
    - Indian Summer, 1952 Aug. 20 (Film-reel 907)
    - Intimate Strangers, 1952 Dec. 10 (Film-reel 908)
    - It's Only Money, 1955 Sept. 14 (Film-reel 1003)
    - Jeannie, 1955 Mar. 16 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Johnny Big, undated (Film-reel 1011)
    - Joy for Mourning, 1952 June 25 (Film-reel 907)
    - Judge Contains Hotel, 1955 May 11 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Lace on Her Petticoat, 1952 Aug. 13 (Film-reel 907)
    - Letters to Lucerne, 1952 Sept. 10 (Film-reel 907)
    - Look What's Going On, 1958 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 1008)
    - Look What's Going On, 1958 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 1011)
    - Low Water at Hellgate, undated (Film-reel 1011)
    - Man in a Trance, undated (Film-reel 1011)
    - Man in Authority, 1958 Apr. 2 (Film-reel 1008)
    - Material Witness, 1958 Feb. 19 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Material Witness, 1958 Feb. 4 (Film-reel 1011)
    - Meet a Body, 1955 July 27 (Film-reel 1003)
    - Melody Jones, 1952 Nov. 5 (Film-reel 908)
    - Men of Prey, 1957 May 22 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Michael & Mary, 1952 Oct. 1 (Film-reel 907)
    - Mock Trial, 1956 Sept. 5 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Most Blessed Woman, 1957 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Mr. Barry's Etchings, 1952 Sept. 3 (Film-reel 907)
    - Mr. Lazarus, 1952 Nov. 26 (Film-reel 908)
    - Mrs. O'Brien Entertains, 1952 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 905)
    - Mrs. O'Brien Entertains, 1952 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 906)
    - Murder of a Sand Flea, 1956 Oct. 10 (Film-reel 1004)
    - My Aunt Daisy, 1955 June 15 (Film-reel 1002)
    - My Lady Ruth, 1955 Dec. 7 (Film-reel 1001)
    - Night of Rain, 1957 Apr. 24 (Film-reel 1011)
    - Night of the Plague, 1957 Mar. 20 (Film-reel 1002)
    - No Riders, 1956 Apr. 18 (Film-reel 1004)
    - No Warning, 1957 Jan. 16 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Nothing Personal, 1957 June 19 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Now Where Was I, 1955 Apr. 13 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Number Four with Flowers, 1955 Nov. 2 (Film-reel 1001)
    - Once a Genius, 1955 Nov. 30 (Film-reel 1001)
    - One, 1955 Oct. 26 (Film-reel 1003)
    - One Dark Night, 1957 Nov. 29 (Film-reel 1011)
    - One Hill, One River, 1955 Jan. 5 (Film-reel 1000)
    - One Way West, 1956 Aug. 1 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Out to Kill, 1956 Sept. 19 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Outline for a Television Play, 1957 July 9 (Film-reel 1011)
    - Paper Foxhole, 1956 Apr. 4 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Paper Moon, 1952 Dec. 31 (Film-reel 908)
    - Patterns, 1955 Jan. 12 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Patterns (repeat), 1955 Feb. 9 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Philip Goes Forth, 1952 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 905)
    - Portrait of a Citizen, undated (Film-reel 1011)
    - Prairie Night, 1956 July 25 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Prologue to Glory, 1952 May 21 (Film-reel 906)
    - Quiet Wedding, 1952 Nov. 19 (Film-reel 908)
    - Run Joe Run, 1958 Jan. 29 (Film-reel 1007)
    - September Tide, 1952 Mar.27 (Film-reel 906)
    - Shadow of Evil, 1956 Sept. 12 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Shadow of Suspicion, 1956 Nov. 7 (Film-reel 1004)
    - She Stoops to Conquer, 1952 May 7 (Film-reel 906)
    - Sheriff's Man, 1957 Mar. 27 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Six By Six, 1952 Aug. 6 (Film-reel 907)
    - Six Hours of Terror, 1957 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Snapfinger Creek, 1956 Feb. 22 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Someone to Hang, 1955 June 8 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Southwest Corner, 1955 Mar. 30 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Spur of the Moment, 1955 Aug. 3 (Film-reel 1003)
    - Starfish, 1956 June 27 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Tear Open the Skies, 1956 July 4 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Teddy Bear, 1956 Dec. 12 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Battle for Wednesday, 1958 Jan. 1 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Beautiful Time, 1955 Oct. 5 (Film-reel 1003)
    - The Braveness of Christy Fallon, 1955 May 18 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Bride the Sun Shines On, 1952 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 906)
    - The Chess Game, 1955 Aug. 31 (Film-reel 1003)
    - The Curly-Headed Kid, 1957 June 26 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Day of the Hunter, 1956 Nov. 21 (Film-reel 1004)